The effect is not very good
Because it's different, it's just that you have a body shape, an ordinary body shape model may be a little better
If you have models of all kinds of models and you have to adapt to them, it's more troublesome
Then we have to sit outside this horse
I remember my first live broadcast was the pilot jacket
Then someone asked me how to do the pilot jacket
Then I thought this thing was a very simple thing, why do you have to learn this, I don't understand
In fact, I think a tactical pilot jacket like this is very easy to do
Because it is a very hard foundation
Then there are some soft packaging materials outside
It actually does it very quickly
Like me, I just use the back panel
Then bring a panel out and use a 3D drawing tool to draw some small lines
Then adjust the shape
The basic version still uses a hard fabric
For example, like that kind of fabric
Then adjust its shape
And its size
In fact, when making a white pilot model
You mainly have to find the right texture of this fabric
Then include the wrinkles we just said
You can add wrinkles through this shrink to
Or through the positive rule
So the wrinkles created along the seam line
When these wrinkles add up in the later stage of your material
It's easy to see
So when you make wrinkles in the early stage
Don't feel like
Hey, I seem to have a lot of wrinkles
Should I remove some of them
That's not the case
When you make the light after the material
Some wrinkles are gone
You know
When you do it, you have to think about it a little bit
After you add the material
Will it be like that kind of fabric
The kind of material that is very flowery
Will it eat up its wrinkles
So sometimes it's not very difficult to have more wrinkles
Okay, and now it's time to install this belt
What about this part of the belt
I just pulled the length of this length
Then change it little by little
Shorten it like this
Oh, the way to make this scarf
I skipped this part of the scarf
Because the scarf is
There is only a scarf in the first lesson of our lesson
Just go to that skill share
The first lesson
You know how to make this scarf
Super easy
Just a very simple method
So there is no talk here
Okay, then I still want to
Our basic version
Is made of a harder material
There is a loop
There is blood in the upper left corner
There will be a recording of the live broadcast this time
Can be added to the back stage
Make the big shape first
After the big shape is done
Then those fenghuo lines
These are just
I studied this tactical backpack later
I see their fenghuo line
It seems to be hidden inside
So let's do it again
Before the inner line
Sew it to the inner line
Because there is a recording
So the little friends who don't watch the live broadcast
My recording
Let me tell you
It must be very late
I used to always
Next week
It's just
It's just a little bit
As a result
Of course you don't watch it
I'm angry
I
Teacher loves work
This one
I haven't considered this direction for the time being
Then adjust the fenghuo line
One by one
I will take this video next week
Upload the video
When the time comes, you must
Leave me a message below
But I had a question before
That is, when you watch the playback
Will you
I hope I put the barrage out
Because if there is no
Wait a minute
It's our base
It's
This version is doing the basic version
I use
The fabric of the cloth
Then the fabric of the cloth
Its bending strength is actually not very high
It will still have some wrinkles
If you want it to be particularly hard
Basically it's this basic board
Its material is particularly
No wrinkles
Just put it
The bending strength is a little higher
it is good
and then
Because there is a barrage
Just
If there is a barrage
I won't talk to the air
Because if I don't put the barrage
Just some
Some friends watching the broadcast
He can't see the barrage
My speech is like talking to the air
Okay
Then I won't put the barrage first
and then
Now you can see
I made this basic version
Is relatively flat
We can add it later
Those wrinkles
Out
Then we increase the bending strength
Just to make it
Just the whole
Just the side
The curve is relatively smooth
Because if you bend the strength
If it's low
It looks like it might be
It's not like that
This is just a basic version
Then we will be on the outside of the basic version
Do another
Just the outer ones
The one with the fabric structure
version
Okay
Then if we are on this version
To create some
Uh
The inner line
These lines
Then if we want the dragon layer
Just go inside the dragon
So when everyone is doing the dragon layer
There is a concept
Is not to affect
Those lines that are in harmony with him
Um
Including the side
We can make a board
Ah, this board
That's what we will do at the end
Based on this board
Make some bags for him on the side
Uh
Is it very troublesome when the inner sewing thread is torn?
Now there is a smart top
It can be torn along the inner line
So it's actually okay
And what I did
Um
As long as you don't have that kind of curve
It should be fine
Or you just don't do it like me
So many curve points
You can make a more flat
More straight
It may be more convenient for you
Okay
Like me here
Go to the dragon layer first
And then you see
For example
If we are here
First the dragon layer
Then you are in the joint version
These outside circles
These
The inner sewing thread will automatically disappear
You just need to add a circle manually
There is more work to do
So remind everyone
That's what we said before
Uh
If you have a complete version
It's before the dragon layer
Combine it first
Then in the dragon
Then you will say
Ah, teacher
Then why do you really want to give it to him
Combine the dragon first
Ah
Because if I combine the dragon first
If I combine it
I'm inside
That layer
He is still
It's inside
This layer
He still has a symmetrical relationship
If we do some other processing later
It can also be processed
Just
In fact, no matter how you do it
It's okay
Because
In our software
You have to
There are a lot of compensation measures
You have a lot of different kinds of tools
And I did this in the previous period
When I made a tactical vest
I was thinking
What kind of tactical vest do I want to do
I see people doing tactical vests
Lin Langman
All kinds of
Ah
Then because we just used it directly
The back version
It itself has this shrink
We have to put the basic version
That shrink
Just modify it to half and half
Then the outer layer
We need it to have this fabric
Ah
We can give him
Change a fabric
Physical properties
For example
Polisher
The fabric of the blouse
Ah
This fabric
It itself is
The stretch performance is relatively poor
It's easier to make fine wrinkles
And then
His curve is not very high
So his wrinkles won't be smoothed
Ah
But there will be some wrinkles outside
It will be like some fabrics
He will have
It's like wrinkles
And then it's still the same
We can improve the fabric that is on the outside
Ah
Just put it down
Shrink like this
Then the inner layer
Don't know
The inner layer of the board
Just don't care about it
Just do it one by one
If you think there are too many wrinkles
Ah
You can manually
This shrink
Repair it again
Good
The side board
If so
We can jump over the fast mirror here
Like the board here
It's also very convenient to sit up
Is you
Give it to him first
Just make a size
Then
Then a little bit
Just change it back
Then
The pocket here in the front
What about
I made one
Is the stick of the board
So this board
I used free powder to sew it
Because he wore one more
Ah
In fact
Is this structure
This structure
What do you want to do
Just can
Because of the tactical background
You don't have to follow me
This process
Just
What do you want to do
Just do it
Because he has a lot of pockets
All kinds of pockets
You want
For example, you want to do that
Put the gun
Then you can do it
Full-size
That shape
Just you don't need to do one
Horizontal vertical pocket
Then my words here
Because I made this pocket at the end
Ah
Just this one
This one
There is also a piece of board
He sewed on the base
This one
Ah
The color of rice
On the board
Outside
It's equivalent to
There is also a layer of pockets here
So I
Just in it
I made him one
Electric
This piece
Board
Ah
What I did in the video
This is the electric board
it is good
Then
I'm still
Give him a copy sticker
And then
Expansion of the strip
It's still the way of making pockets
Well, let's do this
I think you should If everyone
Then
I think you should
If you are
I think that
You all know, right? Expand the Y-axis of the board, then choose the five corners, and then expand the number, that is, if you want to have a fold, then expand two, if you don't need to have a fold, it's just like a small box, then you can just have one, and then here's a little bit for you to mention, oh, it's because if we are in harmony with the internal line, the default Frenzy line type can only be turned, but now this board is an independent board, let's take a look.
This piece of board, is it an independent board? It's not easy to do, don't do ancient soldiers in Marvelous Designer, look at the hard surface modeling, just do the hard surface modeling, don't disperse in our software, that is, if you press the head, you have to do it, but it's not convenient, including some of the lines, that is, those things, for example, like iron, or some of the lines, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it, you can do it.
The armor, it has to have a carved content on it, so you might as well go to other software for multidimensional modeling, because this is a single board, and then if we want to sew this pocket on this single board, its Frenzy line is default Custom Angle, and Custom Angle, its Frenzy line is default 180 degrees, so we can set it to 90 degrees, so it will be folded into a more obvious right angle, understand?
Because, because this board, it is now an independent board, it is not the inner line on the board, if you are the inner line, then it doesn't matter, because the inner line, it has only one Frenzy line type, it is TURN, TURN is folding, although the difference is not very big, but it needs to be clearly known to everyone, that is, the lines that are folded between independent boards, they can be set in a folding angle to do different effects,
they should be placed like this
.
relative to the other side of the package here, we will make some Whoops, like our So, is this package inside there, which is somewhere close to whoops, Rouge,
I like
you
still like
before you do those до ye
there do
so that there will be a seam line between the internal lines
that we come to show the effect of those pull
these, and the fine pleats
have these, that is, the seam line on the internal line will be better
and then, including because I want to do is the effect of the magic stick
so I have the inside of the version of this rectangle of the internal line
is not the outside of the line is not seen
good, then we do that tape, in fact, the tape is very difficult
tape you are to draw some of the inside of the line
and then copy and paste when you press the right button
can be at the same time to copy and paste a lot of roots
and then draw a rectangle
with it almost
good, almost after we have to draw the inside of the line
here, then we can put the display type of the 2D window
into full transparent surface
and then draw the inside of the line
and then copy and paste
and then adjust the number of this is good
good, so we can not go to control the inside of the line
and the inside of the line between the border is how much
can be drawn directly
and then sew them down
good
, then we put the whole
here to say
you have not seen my selection of the point is orange
is because I activated the center point
center point is what
we are now in a normal situation
to select a board
we go to the time when you drag this foot
when you drag this foot
is based on this direction to the
point is fixed to the point is fixed to the point
see no
right
good
that we want based on the center point to the surrounding to the place
we need to double click this center point
after activating the center point
drag the selection box
it is based on the center point to the place of rotation
and also the rotation of this
center point later with everybody mentioned this usage
and then center point, then middle this point
is to place the others in other places
that is to say we can based on this point to rotate
understand this function
that good
For example, let's draw an inner line and switch to the edit dot tool.
After selecting this inner line, double click.
This center point can not only be placed on a corner of the inner line to rotate.
We can also put it in other places and rotate around this point.
Although this function is not yet known where it can be used, it is still useful.
In fact, the longest way to use it is to use it on the center point when it is used to shrink the panel.
We will shrink it on both sides of the center point.
Sometimes these functions will be used when you don't expect it.
After shrinking, because we have a length difference,
it will have such an effect after having these powder lines.
Because the particle diameter is relatively large, its transition is not very harmonious.
Let's reduce the particle diameter a little bit.
See how much content we talk about.
We talked quite fast today, a little faster than I thought.
Maybe because today's friends are more active and smart.
Then we can adjust this now.
OK, let's talk about this.
I observed them doing these bandages.
When it is on the side, sometimes it will roll in.
It will roll in here and roll in to this.
You can't create a powder line directly.
It is easy to wear because it is a flat panel.
Now it is a flat panel.
So we will draw an inner line first.
Then use the folding arrangement tool to fold it back.
Then we sew it again.
Folding arrangement tool.
Click this line.
Give it a pre-folding first.
So when we sew it with a powder line,
the powder line will not pass the panel,
causing the panel to be twisted.
Can you understand?
It also helps to reduce our particle diameter a little bit.
Because if your particle diameter is too large,
for example, like the default 20,
then it will be folded in this way.
It will be folded in this way.
The grid is not enough.
It can't be folded.
It's easy to be unstable.
Do you understand?
OK.
After the project is pre-folded and simulated,
it will automatically be folded and sealed.
Just do it like this.
Then after you finish one,
you just copy and paste it and put it down.
It can be used repeatedly.
You don't have to do it one by one.
And like this pocket,
after you finish a whole set,
you can delete these two.
Then copy and paste it directly and put it over.
I did it here because
when I did it in the early stage,
I didn't want to add a bandage on it.
I suddenly wanted to add it.
So it was done later.
OK.
Here we copy and paste it.
Let's copy and paste it.
And then sew it for him.
This is six.
Six of the mahjong.
Laugh to death.
Then.
Then just do the upper pocket.
In the upper pocket,
in fact,
there is nothing to say.
It's just a different size.
Various rectangles.
Then I still pick up the board.
Then.
Then the board is completely expanded and sealed.
Then, including our sewing,
there are some magic stickers.
When the structure.
Like here.
Let's get him to do that first.
These internal lines of the structure.
In fact, I think.
We draw this internal line.
In fact, many times it can help us quickly.
Enrich your this.
Enrich your this version of the effect.
Sometimes you don't do so much internal line.
Look at the board.
It's a little strange.
After doing these internal lines,
you can help you understand.
I will help you understand when I will add some bright lines and where I will put them later.
For me, I will press Alt4 on the 3D window and open the transparency map,
so that I can quickly match the position of the inner line.
Then just sew it again.
Usually, entertainment is not buying, it is playing games.
It is very effective to combine labor and art.
Including the cover, we can draw an inner line here,
and then set the folding angle,
so that it is folded into a sharper and more obvious fold angle.
For example, if we set it to 120,
it means that the front is protruding outward,
and the corner is a 120 degree angle.
This will have a folding effect.
Of course, this folding effect depends on you.
Do you want it to be bent down directly,
or do you want it to be folded and bent down?
Because all pockets are basically flat,
the effect of folding may be a little different.
Like this.
Then for the bag,
we will not use the same fabric as that.
We will lower its bending strength a little bit,
so that it looks not too hard,
and there is some fabric feeling.
So we will lower its bending strength a little bit.
So for physical properties,
everyone just needs to have a concept.
We will have a default fabric,
but we will follow the ideal.
The ideal effect is to modify its physical properties.
In fact, everyone is following me a little bit.
You will find that in fact,
it is really not as troublesome as you imagine it to be.
And the military outfit actually works very quickly.
Like me,
if I make such a set of clothes,
it's almost,
if it's not a video,
it will take about a day or two to make it.
If you wear it for editing,
maybe three or four days.
Of course, if you follow my tutorial,
you are not so familiar with it,
it doesn't matter.
You do it for a week or so.
One or two weeks.
So I want to see the homework you teach later.
In fact, it is to urge homework.
Then we will give you a structure.
Because everyone usually says,
I want to make this kind of button, button, pull ring structure on my bag.
How to make this button, button, pull ring structure?
So we added another button, button, pull ring structure here.
To make the structure of the buckle.
In fact, this buckle.
I don't know if you have seen this buckle.
I made this buckle with a board.
This buckle is made of a board.
Board pin.
A long, long time ago,
I was still working in the CLO team at that time.
At that time, I felt that
it was very interesting to match this structure with a board.
So this buckle is actually made of a board.
A buckle with different bleeding thickness.
These are a set of buckles.
Bleeding effect.
The final bleeding effect.
I have talked about it in the preview of today's live broadcast.
Have sent.
Good.
At the beginning of the video.
Wait a minute.
Let me take a look.
Where are we talking about now?
1 hour and 06 minutes.
This is the final bleeding effect.
In fact, I actually showed a few pictures at the end.
In our sharing video.
Not a sharing video.
In this dynamic of sharing.
You can see the bleeding effect of each part.
Hey.
Good.
Then do the buckle.
It's the same.
The position of our fold.
Just draw a line for him in advance.
Fold the inner line first.
Then sew it up for him.
Folding like this.
The strength of the particle is reduced.
And then the impact thickness is reduced.
Like this relatively small version.
It doesn't matter if you reduce the strength of the particle in the early stage.
And you will find that my file.
My habit will be divided into projects.
Just do a few project files.
For example, the top is one.
Then the bag is one.
The pants is one.
I did it separately.
Because you are at the same time.
Even if you are frozen.
The version.
He will still have the calculation.
Because the frozen version.
He is not completely that.
Anti-activated.
If it is completely anti-activated.
Your computer operation speed.
It can be saved.
It's obvious.
But if it's frozen.
Because he will still calculate.
This version of the collision.
So even if you are fully frozen.
That is, it will still.
It will affect your computer.
The speed of operation.
So the project file.
I will do a few.
And then this.
Because of this.
This.
This is a practice.
Okay.
All right.
Even if the bag is also supuesto.
The same.
The bag is interspersed with the clothes.
So my clothes and the bag are made together.
Good.
And then.
Here, notice.
We have the fold at this side.
Just.
Is.
Fold with this folding arrangement tool.
Forced it to fold it.
The folding process tool.
It's a good thing.
After we have done the folding.
For example.
I now think.
He folded this one.
Too small.
Too short.
Then our.
Uh.
Daily operations.
Is to stretch it.
Ceiling.
Wait a minute, I'll pour some water
Okay, our daily operation is to lengthen this board
The lengthening of the board is like this
Because in Marvelous Designer
When you go to modify a board
For example, whether you are a retractable board or an extended board
It will go along the original trend of this edge
That is to say, sometimes people will say
Why can't I lock it in the 3D window
It's not a long-term old card
It's because I'm in a pause
I'm going to laugh to death
It's not a long-term old card, it's because I'm in a pause
I'm laughing to death
No, it's because in our software
You go to lock a board
Or say
When you pull a board
For example, this board I have now
Is the model of this form
Then I will extend this edge to you again
It is extended along its original grid
So its trend
Sometimes it's not a flat board
Its trend is not a flat trend
It's this kind of bendy stretch
You know, it's going to be deformed seriously
Like me
If we pull it up
Does it go out
If you just simulate it
It's going to be like this
Oh my God
It's starting to shake
It's starting to be unstable
So we say
We have to use the selection grid tool
In this case
We have to prevent from being unstable
We pull this board out first
It's not a good choice to choose a board
So let's go to the second draw
After the choice
The board that passes through
Give it first
pull it out, and then simulate it
. It won't be unstable like this. Do you understand?
Understand? Because just now
we extended this board directly,
it has already been folded, that is, passed through,
and then you extend and stretch it again,
select the grid tool, select the grid tool,
the mouse is placed here, there is a fixed needle,
the top is selected grid, this tool
in our skill sharing video
has also talked about this tool's special use,
it is used to pull the grid in an orderly manner,
and then to deal with some insertion problems,
like our side,
just now we extended the position, it went through,
and there are many structures like pockets,
you just wear a lot of layers of fabric,
it will be unstable,
understand?
And
it is added to this folding structure,
it is not sure that it is
you, after you start the simulation,
you are late to deal with it,
we are better to deal with it before the simulation,
pull the board out, you know,
this is to do the side pocket,
the side pocket is actually really hard,
it is
not more than five minutes to do this bag, okay?
That is, you give it to him,
pull the board out,
and then give him a little exaggeration for five minutes,
not more than 20 minutes,
just give him the board outline to expand,
and then you have to pay attention,
like this whole circle,
when the board outline is expanded,
remember to select the point,
or don't choose the five corners,
otherwise it will have problems with its expansion,
we choose the default corner,
okay, after the board outline is expanded,
we sew it up,
in fact, you look at us,
this is to do the side pocket is a repeat of the operation,
it is not very difficult,
it is just more,
well, more repetitive,
and then the side pocket is,
our 100% external expansion of the function is like this,
ah,
the final effect we want is,
this bag, it can pass independently,
it can pass independently, it can pass independently,
and then it only has one part,
and our tactical vest is mixed together,
so we just draw a circle of that line first,
and then expand its board outline,
so that we only sew this side and this side,
understand?
So that our bag is not too flat,
and stick it on the inside layer,
right,
and then we copy and paste this board again,
you can copy and paste it in the 3D window,
so that the two bags will be,
you can adjust their positions,
if you copy and paste it in the 2D window,
you can't be sure how far apart the bag is,
not to say how far apart,
is it close to them,
then repeat and paste in the 3D window, you can make them both stay closer, then we use this,
I will use this long-sleeve line to create a long-sleeve pattern to sew it up.
Of course, I am used to the software, and I can sew it up very quickly in the 2D window.
If you are not sure, you can move the pattern to the vicinity of these two bag patterns first,
and then use the 3D sewing tool to sew it up.
Of course, I actually think the 2D sewing is faster.
This pattern, let me talk about the length of this edge.
I calculated from this point to this point in this circle.
So when I sew it, it's like this.
Sew this edge here to here, and then sew this edge here to here.
And then I'm going to make a zipper on top.
So I divided it into two long-sleeve patterns.
The bag pattern is more of a test of your three-dimensional structure.
In fact, it's not very difficult to make a knife.
And then it includes our sewing line.
The fold angle of the sewing line here can be set.
For example, if it is 120 degrees, it is a fold line that protrudes out frontally.
And it's more sharp, and it's more obvious to have such a hard fold.
So,
And then,
In a while, we'll show you another fold angle.
The sewing line can also be set to a fold angle.
Just like the inner line.
And then we sew up the outer layer of this pattern.
And then add to the side function.
You can automatically paste it on top of it.
And then simulate it.
Now we're going to do the surface flip.
Why do we need to flip the surface?
It's like this.
Let's take a look.
Uh,
A friend of mine said,
Hey, why can't I see the thickness of my home?
Ah, you can't see the thickness of your home because you didn't open the thickness display.
Press Alt1 to open the thickness display.
And then press Alt2.
It's like this in my video.
No thickness display.
When you don't open the thickness display.
It's called the texture surface.
The texture surface is used to observe the fabric.
The front and back of the fabric.
It's like we're folding these things.
That's what we did before.
It's all back to the outside.
These positions.
When we were making the bag.
When we were sewing it just now.
I didn't care.
It's back to the outside.
Right?
When we actually pour it out.
I hope it's front to the outside.
So this version.
We're going to turn it over.
Let it face out.
That's the direction it's facing.
It's facing out.
So I'll choose it.
After that.
It's called the surface flip.
In fact, the surface flip.
The English word for this word is flip normal.
It's the opposite of the line.
Okay.
After we sew it up.
We can set it up.
This one.
Folding angle of the sewing line.
Okay.
Just like I just said.
The folding angle of the sewing line.
When it's 180 degrees.
It's facing out.
And it's going to be more sharp.
Including the sewing line on our side.
If you want to make a harder bag.
And then it's this fold angle.
The fold sides are more obvious.
When it's more square.
You can set this.
Well, it's 180 degrees.
It could be 90.
Or a fold angle of 120.
Then we do.
The zipper.
If you want the zipper.
Choose the inner line.
Then cut it.
Cut and sew it.
And then the middle part.
Let's draw another one in the middle.
Cut and sew the inner line.
Then reduce the diameter.
Reduce the thickness.
In fact, these are all regular operations.
And then you can see.
I can't use the panel.
I'm frozen.
Okay.
Then we draw some inner lines.
Because of the bag.
It's basically a double-layer structure.
So we're also in the Cologne layer.
I'll draw some inner lines for him.
Including some of our sewing lines.
These.
I might use the inner line first.
To make it fit.
So that when I do those lines.
I'll have a concept.
I'm almost at this position.
Add a line.
Okay.
Then we'll put it.
It's just a thicker version.
Increase the thickness of the collar.
So that the zipper in the middle.
It looks like a thin piece.
It's like.
You know.
You go and observe.
The zipper on the bag.
It's going to be.
If you do it thicker outside.
The zipper is a little bit lower.
So we're going to put it outside.
Increase the thickness of the collar.
A little bit.
Okay.
Actually, let's look at the bag.
Now let's take a look at this bag.
This bag.
Now we.
It's still set at 120 degrees.
Folding angle.
So this fold is more.
It's more.
Because it's.
The front is protruding outwards.
Then it folds.
It's more sharp.
Just like we just talked about.
Then I actually.
The last one I made.
This bag.
This fold line.
There's a little bit of that.
It's a little bit of that.
It's a little bit softer.
The overall feeling of this bag.
The texture is that.
It's loose.
It's a little bit loose.
The texture of this bag is that.
It's loose and wide.
It's softer.
Right?
Because we'll be back.
I'm going to change it.
This folding angle.
Because I went to see it.
That is.
They are.
It's the bag of the military.
What about his bag?
Give me the feeling.
It's all the middle of the seam line.
It's in the inside.
The line.
Like this.
If the seam line.
We will set the seam line angle.
Set it to.
Bigger than 180 degrees.
So it's a little bit.
It's a little bit.
Bigger than 180 degrees.
It's okay to see the possible.
Because you've been watching our live broadcast for a long time.
It's going to be the end of the live broadcast.
So if you're tired now.
Add a mirror.
Ah.
We'll take this one.
I'm almost done.
All right.
Then the outer layer.
The outcome is.
Anyway, it's all some conventional operations.
Come on.
Now let's take a look at this fold.
This fold.
As we just said.
It's set to 120 degrees.
It's facing out.
And now we're going to set it up.
To.
Bigger than.
120 degrees.
Just.
Right.
You can see that this bag is slowly, slowly, does it have that feeling of bending into the inside, bending into the inside of the sewing line?
This is our folding angle, the folding angle of the sewing line, the effect that can be achieved, isn't it?
We have some, like our book bag, or this kind of plastic bag, it has some, it is the sewing line, it has that kind of bending into the inside, and then there is a little bone on both sides, right?
We are using this, uh, the folding angle of the sewing line that is greater than 180 degrees.
Uh, there is a replay, there is a replay, and you can pay attention to our Bilibili account.
We will have a lot of tutorials, and you can, uh, private message the background, and then add our skirt, like this.
Let's set the folding angle, and then wait for it to simulate it.
Now this bag,
it will have a soft feeling, right?
It's not as hard as it was just now, and then the fold is so sharp.
Isn't it amazing?
Now the overall texture of this bag is softer, and we will have inner and outer layers of panels.
Then we can modify its fabric, and then make it look like a more,
that is to say, a fabric that is hard to wear.
And then here,
this thing like this,
this part,
I will add my nipples, my nipples, and here is a space on my side,
here is a slot so that I can see the lid,
anyway my god,
helmet,
my heart,
Our courses are all free courses, there are paid courses, but you can watch them for free first.
Paid courses are our, or I recommend you to watch our free courses first, because our free courses are really hard work.
Just take a look at the free courses, you will learn everything you need to learn.
Here, let's take a look at the shoulder.
I saw that there are a lot of military backpacks, they all have one here, although I don't know what this thing is called.
But this thing is supposed to be used to prevent sliding, which is a folding structure in the shoulder position.
So let's do it here.
When you do the folding structure, you can use the selection network tool to pull it, and then you can arrange it directly with the board.
Press it down, press it down.
And then reduce the particle diameter.
Okay, reduce the particle diameter.
Let's reduce it first.
Oh, the load-bearing shock absorber.
Okay, I learned it.
This is called the load-bearing shock absorber.
Okay.
And then, including when we are touching the conflict thickness of the fabric.
Because this board has been pressed very tight.
You know, it's easy to be unstable.
.
When the board is pressed tight.
At this time, we will reduce the thickness of the conflict.
The board around it is used to wrap the board to prevent the conflict.
This layer of air thickness is weakened.
If we suddenly shrink this value too much.
For example, from 2.5 to 1.
It has an obvious shaking.
We just had an obvious shaking, didn't we?
So what do we need to do?
Reduce it a little bit.
Don't reduce it too much at a time.
About the knowledge of physical properties.
In fact, I will bring you a little bit of what I can bring in each lesson.
Just do it with it.
You can do it slowly.
You will have this concept.
Still have to do more.
Okay.
So we don't want to reduce the conflict thickness to 1 at a time.
We can reduce it to 2 first.
Then reduce it to 1.5.
Finally, reduce it to 1.
Like this.
I think this.
I think this structure in my imagination.
It should be to increase the volume of the pressure.
It's just that.
It may be a little bit wider.
It may not be so heavy when it is wrapped.
Then, including when we make the structure.
You have to think about it in advance.
I'm not going to wrap it directly here.
Because after it is wrapped.
It's just a very tight structure, isn't it?
If we have a tight structure.
At this time.
It's going to be a double-layer structure.
That is to say.
It may affect the stability.
We just put this layer of cloth first.
Put it on the bottom first.
And then put the structure of this board on it.
Do it well.
It's a cologne layer of cologne.
Then include us.
After the cologne layer comes out.
Here we will also use different fabrics.
There is a side.
We will use a harder fabric.
That is the side of the bottom.
I use a harder fabric.
Then this side of the outside.
I may use a softer fabric for it.
Including its physical properties.
What is soft?
That is, the strength of the cologne.
I may reduce it a little bit.
Reduce the tension of the line of contact.
Then the bend strength is also.
Because.
Later we will give it more pressure.
These two panels will add pressure.
I have talked about it in our tutorial before.
The role of pressure.
In fact, it has something to do with the wear of the fabric.
Just like you.
The stretch performance is also a bit of a relationship.
Just like you go to blow the plastic bag and blow the balloon.
It's different.
You can only blow the plastic bag that big.
But your balloon can blow very big.
The same.
You can blow the balloon from such a small one to such a big one.
Just because.
The stretch performance of the balloon is very good.
But the stretch performance of the plastic bag is very poor.
So everyone should be able to understand.
So you are also giving a pressure.
Then you have to make it more bone.
More obvious.
You must be able to pull this layer of fabric.
Stretch performance.
That is, the tension of the right foot line and that.
The strength of the neckline has to be reduced.
As long as you give that pressure.
It can be like this.
More soft.
Then.
There will be some dents here.
There are some dents in the seam line.
effect.
Including.
We can put this plate.
Increase the thickness of the conflict.
ah.
on the one hand.
You can increase the pressure value a little bit.
On the one hand.
Except for pressure.
Also that.
The thickness of theworking was also fearful.
Influenced.
Because the thickness of the conflict was also similar.
It's just that you're in the plate.
Add a layer of air to it.
So.
Add a layer of body words the way.
You can see that I put it there.
The thickness of the conflict.
After maximizing.
Aogle concentration pavilion of position.
It does not count adhesion thickness.
For him.
After adding the impact thickness, it is also like adding a thin sponge pad.
Then simulate
You can see that the physical properties of the outer version and the inner version are obviously different
There are some soft and airy components on the outer layer, but the inner layer is very flat
Because the material on the inner layer is relatively hard
Then we need to fold it
In fact, folding is relatively easy
To fold, you can use the panel line expansion and the folding arrangement tool to fold it over
Pay attention to the order of folding
Fold the two layers first
Then simulate
Then fold the other layer
Just like folding a quilt
It's almost like folding a quilt
Fold it up with it
Then the other side is the same
Fold it over with the folding arrangement tool
Then borrow the pattern
After that, we can use a sewing needle to fix it
Or you can use a sewing line to fix it
I just stole it here
I don't seem to have a double-layer structure
So I'll just use that
I seem to use the thickness directly to show the double layer
If you don't steal it, you can do it with the double-layer
Okay
Then I will put this in the middle
I will finally delete the inner line of this folding
Then reduce the particle diameter
I still made a double layer
It seems that I am not lazy
This file
This file is what I did yesterday or the day before yesterday
I forgot
Laugh to death
Oh, the teacher's memory is not very good
Okay
Then we also use the other layer
It's not the same
In fact, the operation is not bad
Then here we use the seam allowance
Pay attention
If you just use point-to-point seam allowance
Point-to-point seam allowance
Because it is a point of strength
So it is a point of strength
It will be more obvious
This strength point
You see
Especially this kind of tight version
This strength point will be more obvious
In this kind of obvious situation
We can modify the length of its line
To adjust
For example, after I use the edge seam allowance here
In fact, the seam allowance is between the points
You can set the length
In addition
You can also use this line seam allowance
We just sew a whole edge and a whole edge together
Just sew it together
Just sew
Laugh to death
In fact, the seam allowance is similar to drawing this inner line
Then sew
It's just that the modern seam allowance is more intuitive
Because if you draw the inner line
Sometimes you have to align the inner line
Then we use the modern seam allowance
Just wait for it to be sewn
If you want to make it more soft
Right
Then we can use the editing seam allowance tool
Select here
Then set the length of the line for it
So you can set these two points
That's the distance between the seam allowance lines
The distance between them
For example, the length of my line is 3
Then between them
The distance between this edge and this edge is 3 mm
Can you understand
This is a bit softer
So actually using the modern seam allowance
You can not only
Whether it's a modern seam allowance
Or a point-to-point seam allowance
You can use this tool
The length of the line
To adjust
The effect you want
It's a bit similar to the rule
How much is the distance between these two points
Or the distance between these two lines
How much is the distance
You can set it like this
Okay, that's about it
And then sometimes
If you want it to be tighter
Maybe just use the sewing allowance
To deal with it a little more
Adjust it
Okay, then
Because I have frozen other panels
Here's a panel
We just used this
When the ball of the other side is used
It's through
Then we use the layer tool
Just put it back
Okay
Isn't it
Well, wait a little bit
ok
Finish here
Thank you
Okay
Here it is
door
ah
work
No
Ray
Roo
Play
Phillips
Roo
I said that the adjustment position is to adjust the insertion between the low-weight
and the lower-weight, so the adjustment position is to adjust the insertion between the low-weight and the lower-weight.